# AIDEN KELLY

## .NET Developer

#### SUMMARY

NET Developer with five years of experience developing web, batch, and business intelligence solutions using ASP.NET, C#.NET, SharePoint, and MS SQL. Expertise in requirements analysis, design, development, testing, maintenance, enhancement, and production support of business applications. Certified Web Development Professional with a deep passion for technology, extensive technological expertise, and well-developed teamwork abilities.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Senior .NET Developer

2018 - Present

### Wyman Ltd

New York, NYC

- MS SQL 2008r2 creating stored procedures, views
- · Worked on MS SQL Server 2005 and 2008, IBM Data Studio
- Fully designed and developed 2 .NET applications used by a team of >10 on daily basis
- Fully designed and developed 2 .NET applications used by a team of >10 on daily basis

Senior .Net Developer

2017 - 2018

Grimes New York, NYC

Grimes is a global leader in the technologies that connect people

- · Working unattended directly under CTO, in a pair of 2
- · Received excellence grade in evaluation consecutively for 4 years
- Upgrade and developed SAR 3 million revenue E-Gov web application to N tier architecture

Senior C# .NET Developer

2016 - 2017

Carroll New York, NYC

Carroll is a Software Developing Company founded on 2015 that delivers ready to use software to different type of clients

- Involved in database design on SQL Server 2008 and development of different database objects containing functions, triggers, store procedures
- · Designed front-end using the latest tools like Ajax
- Designed web pages using HTML, JavaScript, CSS, DHTML, XML and page design and layout and graphics
- · Applied fixes and enhancements to SQL scripts through SQL Server

.NET Developer

2011 - 2015

Heller

New York, NYC

Development company that designs innovative bespoke software services.

- · Communicated with customers to implement Web Services
- Trouble-shot and fixed problems through customer requests, and QA
- · Utilized ASP.NET, VB.NET, AJAX, and Microsoft Visual Studio for development
- Managed work items in Microsoft Team Foundation Server

## CERTIFICATION

### Oracle Database 12c Administrator

Oracle Database technology is used by the world's leading companies to manage critical business functions, systems and processes.

## Microsoft Certified Solutions Developer: App Builder

Validates the skills needed to build modern mobile and/or web applications and services.



#### **SKILLS**

Ajax · C++ · .NET · Java EE · SQL ·

Microsoft Office · .NET Framework ·

SQL Server, HTML .

Client-side web development

# **EDUCATION**

Computer Systems and Technologies, Bachelor

New York University 2008 - 2009

#### **STRENGTHS**



Work well in a team and know how to support my teammates.

## \* Critical Thinking

I always think clearly and rationally, understanding the logical connection between ideas.

### Delivering Results

Focus on the key inputs and deliver them with the right quality and in a timely fashion.

# Problem Solving

I am capable of coming up with creative solutions to identify problems and solve them in an efficient and effective manner.

## **INDUSTRY EXPERTISE**

Microsoft.NET

LAMP & Open Source

Powered by

